Huh?
Back then, why did I...
Good morning.
Welcome. This Is Your New Family Home!
Good morning from the dead of night!
Mayonaka Punch!
Ichiko!
Ding!
How does MayoPan spend a
week-long extended break?
Vlog day two!
For my day off today...
Behold! Meal prep!
Is this a good angle?
Oh, that's perfect!
Seriously?
With Masaki gone, I thought we'd have
a week off from shooting videos.
Well, not exactly.
Masaki-san told us to film what
we do while we're on vacation.
A vacation that we have to film
doesn't count as a vacation!
B-But we only have three months left
until Mother's deadline.
After taking part in that
festival and doing collabs,
we've finally hit 400k subscribers.
We can't be taking a break
at a time like this...
I'm sacrificing my beauty sleep
to work my butt off here!
I think I deserve a little praise!
I-I'm also...
Stop!
Oh, you were still awake?
The more footage we have, the better.
W-Were we disrupting you?
You two.
You're stepping on Live-sama.
She seems awfully upset.
Snap out of it already.
Live-sama, are you still alive?
Masaki <3
Masaki!
I miss you!
You know it's only been two days.
How's today's footage?
Well, I finished making cuts,
but it's a little long.
Okay.
I'll trim it down where I can
when I add the captions.
I'll send what I have, then.
Thanks. See you.
Oh, how's your mom?
Is she okay?
It was her appendix.
She'll be out of the hospital in a week.
Oh, that's a relief!
Sorry to duck out at such a critical time.
No, it's not your fault.
It sure is lonely without you here, though.
Masaki, I really do—
Well, see you.
We should go to sleep soon.
We'll start shooting again when the sun sets.
Good night.
How do I deal with this?
I would have been fine on my own for a week.
What?
If you were busy with NewTube stuff,
you didn't have to come home.
What could I do?
Mom asked me to come back.
My precious winter break...
I would have less chores
to do if I were alone.
I-I was gonna clean that up later.
If I were alone in the house,
I could blast dance music every night
while busting out my sick moves.
What?
I'll handle the laundry,
so do the dishes at least.
Hey, hold it right there.
What?
Sakura, do you watch NewTube?
A little.
Can you take a look at this?
Still images?
Videos.
I asked them to shoot vlogs on their days off,
but all I get back is stuff like this!
They're a real wacky bunch, so I thought
they'd be entertaining on their days off, too.
But if I trash this footage,
we won't have a video for tomorrow.
Uploading every day is a must!
What do I do?
I mean, it does feel like
a realistic day off, but...
It's boring.
How does MayoPan spend a
week-long extended break?
Vlog!
Today, we're going on a drive to the
best spot to enjoy a nighttime view!
Yay!
The catch: we have to eat at every
drive-through we come across.
Will our stomachs hold out until
we reach our scenic destination?
We'll shoot some amazing footage to use!
That's the spot!
You're stiff as a board.
Is it that bad?
Can I stop now?
Not yet! A little more!
Don't stop!
I don't trust you when you say "a little more."
What?
You kept saying, "C'mon, just a little more,"
and then you'd eaten all my ice cream.
How long ago was that?
Literally yesterday.
Coming.
Huh? Why?
We're here!
Ah!
Little sister!
You're Masaki's sister, right?
Oh, you look so young.
Out of my way!
Hey, there!
I've gotten to know your big sister very well!
My name's Live! From Mayonaka Punch!
Her blood smells normal, though.
That's rude to say to someone you've just met.
Oh, wait. Has she not told you?
I'm part of a NewTube channel with your sister!
I know.
Hello. I'm Sakura.
Nice to meet you!
Y-You can tell me what happened inside.
Come in.
So this is Masaki's family home!
The place that birthed Masaki's blood!
Awesome!
Masaki-san, have you always lived here?
No, this used to be my grandma's place.
We moved here after my parents got divorced.
Oh?
Up until preschool, I used to live
close to Banpai Manor, actually.
What?!
So you mean I might've come across
teeny-tiny Masaki in the past?!
That's nothing short of fate!
Destiny!
Fate
So? Why are you here?
Didn't I tell you to film
that night view roadtrip?
We filmed it, all right!
But also...
Here.
Oh! It's so pretty here at night!
No Video Recording
The following actions are strictly prohibited.
- Photography and videos for commercial purposes
- Operating unmanned aircraft,
as well as aerial photography (drones, RC, etc.)
- Photography and videos with selfie sticks
- Extreme acts of photography that disturb others
- Filming of NewTube videos (no exceptions!)
Those found to be in violation will incur a fine of 10,000 yen.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Ack!
Double ack!
Apparently, they recently
banned video recording.
We should discuss with you before
shooting a different video, right?
Time is of the essence, so we
ditched the car and flew over here!
I see... Wait.
Couldn't you have just called?
What? Don't be so cold!
Get off! I can't breathe!
Here you go.
Th-Thanks.
Sakura-chan, got any good ideas?
You're asking her?
It seems like your only choice is
to film something around here.
Here?
If you go somewhere else to film,
you won't have enough
time to edit the video.
Well...
But are there any interesting
places in this area?
Not at all.
It's a normal neighborhood.
Hmm...
Ta-dah!
I've got it!
How about, "I Returned to My Family Home"?
Huh?
Oh, I've seen videos like that.
Where they eat dinner as a family,
or read out letters of gratitude.
Sure to bring warmth to your heart
and a smile to your face!
Sounds good! Not that I'd know.
I thought it'd be impossible, since we
don't have family homes, but you do!
Me?
N-Not happening!
I've never been in any of our videos!
But you could be.
Everyone would throw a fit
if a new face suddenly showed up!
But you're the only one who can!
Please?
Nope! Not a chance!
Aww...
Then...
What do we do?
Wanna go hit up some pachinko?
Hmph.
Live.
Welcome.
This is your family home now.
What?
Standby
The story is, your mother's in the hospital,
so you came back home to take care
of your sister, just like me.
The rest you can feel free to make up.
Okay! I'm ready to go!
Also, don't call Sakura by her real name.
Got it.
Shooting a video pretending that
this is Live-sama's family home...
Masaki sure does comes up with some wild ideas.
Um...
Is it okay to trick our audience like this?
Besides, won't we get busted in no time
if Masaki's friends watch this video?
It's fine.
I've never had a friend come over.
She doesn't have any friends.
Sakura, are you ready, too?
Why are you pouting?
I'm against staged videos.
Hey, just leave it to me.
Good morning from the dead of night!
Mayonaka Punch!
Live here!
Today, we're at my family home!
This here's my little sister!
Hello.
Man, it's so relaxing being back home!
So nostalgic, you could even
call it nostalgia-inducing!
Totally.
Um...
Now that we're back in my family home,
how about a room tour?!
Time to show you all my bedroom!
Bam!
Is my diary here somewhere?
Oh! A photo album!
Where could my school uniform be?
Or maybe some childhood clothes!
What's this place?
Soba Restaurant Tachian
The diner we ate at often as a family...
went out of business and now it's a
soba joint which holds no memories.
Zero memories?!
This is it!
We ate here all the time as kids!
Seven times a week!
So every day.
This shrimp tempura tastes
just like Mom's home cooking!
I could go all day!
Ta-dah!
Let's switch it up!
Bottoms up—
No outside food!
And that's the least of the issues!
Live, you're fired!
Tokage, take over for her!
Tokage!
You need to avenge Live-sama's dead body!
Here we go!
Um, this is my family home.
Here's my sister.
Hello.
Today, I'll be gazing out
at the snow on the veranda,
while lazily reminiscing with
my sister about when we were kids.
Do you remember that game
we used to always play, little sister?
You've never played with me.
What? That can't be right!
Like, what about tag?
Nope.
Playing house?
Hide-and-seek?!
Oh, there was that.
Right? Wasn't it fun?
You were "it," but you left me behind
and went back home.
What?
Okay!
I'll be the one to make you forget
those sad memories!
Jump!
I'll play with you to your heart's content!
What are we doing?
Nothing says snow like a snowball fight!
You're wide open!
Yay! I win!
Bada bing!
Sakura!
Tokage's fired, too!
Ta-dah!
This is my family home!
And making her debut here is my little sister!
Hello.
Stop!
Huh?
She looks older than you,
so you'll be the little sister.
No way!
I've been alive for way longer!
Just do it!
You're older?
And so, I'll be making a dish filled with
memories with my big sister today.
But what food is filled with memories for you?
I know how to make curry.
Go on.
I'd always make it whenever
Mom was late coming home.
But you'd complain about
how underseasoned it was,
and add loads of soy sauce to it.
I do apologize for that!
Then you can just sit back
and wait while I cook!
Today, I'll make a delicious meal
filled with memories for you!
Voilà!
A meal filled with memories!
A hundred years ago, when I was a child,
we couldn't afford lots of food like now.
Mom always shared her fish
with me and my little brother.
But I couldn't bear to see her go hungry,
so I would lie to her,
saying I was full and didn't want any fish.
Huh.
I told her, "You need to eat, Mom,"
as I smiled with teary eyes.
Okay, start!
Um, well...
We're here at my family home.
This is my little sister.
Coming.
What?
What?! You're gonna film this, too?!
Good evening.
Sorry, it's just leftovers.
Thank you as always.
My older sister.
Oh, do forgive me.
My eyes have been failing me lately.
Why, it's been ages.
L-Long time no see.
It's Takeshita-san.
She makes food for us sometimes.
It's good.
Th-Thank you very much
for looking after my sister.
Goodness, I hardly recognize you.
Eek!
You always stole Sakura-chan's New Year's
money and used it to buy toys for yourself.
You sure have grown up.
But there's something about your voice...
W-Well...
Not to mention your height...
U-Um, I-I'm...
I-I'm her bona fide big sister! I swear it!
After all, I've never been wrong in my life!
Bow down before me, peasants!
Yes, yes. That's more like it.
P-Please forgive me for being so rude!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Huh?
I'm nothing like that, am I?
Takeshita-san said she's okay
with being in the video.
Thanks.
What a nice old lady.
Wait, so whose family home
are we saying this is?
Let me have one more chance!
What?
I'll pull it off without a hitch this time!
We haven'y shot the
family-thanking scene yet.
Guess we'll try it again with Live.
Yes!
Okay, let's get started!
Um, I-I've only made it this far
thanks to my family!
Thanks, family. Thanks for real.
Family for life.
Seriously, thank you!
Thank you.
Um, I've caused a lot of trouble
for my little sister.
But I didn't mean any harm by it!
It's more like my personality
is just kind of awful.
I regret all the things I've done!
So please support me going forward!
Is that too much to ask?
Yes.
What?!
You eat my ice cream without asking,
ditch me during hide-and-seek,
complain about my cooking,
and steal my New Year's money.
You only do the things you want to do,
you always act before you think,
you left the house right after graduating
high school and made our mom worry.
When you got booted from your channel,
you were too stubborn to call us.
You really are awful.
So it's too late to ask me for your support.
After all, I've been supporting you
from the very start.
That's a wrap!
Good job, everyone!
Good work!
But we don't have time to relax.
Why? Because this video needs
to go up by tomorrow night!
We'll split up the editing
and tackle it as a group!
Don't count on getting any sleep!
Right!
I'm going to sleep.
Go ahead!
Without further ado,
"Investigation:"
<Investigation>
How well can everyone act when asked to pretend a
crew member's family home is their own family home?!
<Investigation>
How well can everyone act when asked to pretend a
crew member's family home is their own family home?!
"How well can everyone act
when asked to pretend"
"a crew member's family home
is their own family home?!"
Video production starts... now!
What?
It's good!
Sakura, you've gotten better!
I thought you really were
making a staged video.
You know I'd never do that.
You could have let me in on it.
Sorry, sorry.
I'm glad it looks like we'll make it in time.
Hey.
Are you never going to be in a MayoPan video?
What?
Recording
Because of the scandal?
Is it still on your mind?
I enjoy working behind the scenes now.
Sorry for dropping by so suddenly.
Thanks for everything.
See you!
Um, here.
Could I have all of your autographs?
Is one of your friends a
MayoPan fan or something?
I'm your fan.
What?
I misspoke. I'm a huge fan.
What?!
R-Really?!
Seriously?
If you really, really love me that much,
you should have told me.
No, I couldn't possibly.
Does that mean you watch my videos, too?!
Of course.
You were so cute when you teared up
because you messed up your cooking.
I-I wasn't crying!
What about my singing?
It's so wonderful,
I can't even express it in words.
It feels wrong to even try.
Yay!
Sakura-chan!
Say something nice about me as well!
I could do that without even thinking.
Your autographs, please!
Okay, I'm first!
Wait, Tokage!
Don't sign in the middle!
Give me the pink marker!
Leave room for me!
I didn't know you were a fan.
All done!
Ichiko
TOKAGE
Live <3
Sakura-chan, here you go!
Thank you so much.
Good for you.
You, too.
No way. I'm never even on camera.
Hyped-Up Sisters. Mayonaka Punch.
I'm your oldest fan.
You've always been a tough nut to crack.
Live
Sent you a sticker
Goodnight
Masaki!
Live!
And...
Sakura here.
You're so cute, Sakura-chan!
Tiny Masaki! Mini-Masaki!
Well, we do look alike.
No, we don't. Don't ever say that again.
What?
You totally do!
Then yes, we do.
Hey!
Live "Neener, neener!
Shigeyuki, Shigeyuki!"
Next time: "Rampage x Fateful Showdown!"
Rampage x Fateful Showdown!
She's turned into what now?!